OKEZI IKOKENO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



kazdevs@gmail.com

Q ugbowo, benin city.

okezi.netlify.app

github.com/kazdevs

PROFILE

I am a passionate and professional web developer with over 6 years of experience in frontend web development and website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail. I am always ready to learn and willing to push the limits to achieve the required goals.

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- BOOTSTRAP
- SASS
- VERSION CONTROL(GIT)
- TAILWIND
- WORDPRESS

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

federal government college, warri. 2004 - 2010

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

University Of Benin, Benin city.

2016 - 2020

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

What You Need Ventures

2016 - 2018

- Responsive website design
- Scaling, code refactoring, and code optimization
- · App and web testing and optimization

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

@konga

2019-2020

- Responsive websites design
- Beautiful user interfaces that lead to more customer engagement.
- Implementation of better frontend frameworks like react js

TECHNICAL SPECIALIST AND WEB DEVELOPER (IT GUY)

a prince collections inc

2020 - 2021

- Responsive website development.
- Handled everything technical and computer-related
- SEO implementation that increased traffic and sales by over 12%.